<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <VPEH_Bloodfocus.label>кровава зосоредженість</VPEH_Bloodfocus.label>
  <VPEH_Bloodfocus.description>By forcibly manipulating the body’s stores of hemogen, the caster can enter a state of rapid meditation, regaining psyfocus at the cost of hemogen.</VPEH_Bloodfocus.description>

  <VPEH_BloodShard.label>кровавий осколок</VPEH_BloodShard.label>
  <VPEH_BloodShard.description>Launch a small amount of excess blood as a lethal projectile by forcibly expelling hemogen that has been solidified into a crystalline structure.</VPEH_BloodShard.description>

  <VPEH_BloodSpew.label>кровавий плювок</VPEH_BloodSpew.label>
  <VPEH_BloodSpew.description>Spew forth a fine mist of hemogen towards the targets, coating them in sticky, nauseating blood. Those affected are overcome with intense vomiting.</VPEH_BloodSpew.description>

  <VPEH_CloseWounds.label>закрита рана</VPEH_CloseWounds.label>
  <VPEH_CloseWounds.description>Примусово перемістити надлишок крові, щоб зупинити кровотечу.</VPEH_CloseWounds.description>

  <VPEH_Hemodrain.label>висмоктування</VPEH_Hemodrain.label>
  <VPEH_Hemodrain.description>Дистанційно витягує кров цілі та перетворює її на гемоген. Практично, але не ефективно.</VPEH_Hemodrain.description>

  <VPEH_CorpseExplosion.label>трупний вибух</VPEH_CorpseExplosion.label>
  <VPEH_CorpseExplosion.description>Використайте гемоген заклинателя, щоб викликати вибух трупа, який не завдає шкоди, але створює щільний туман крові, який викликає сильну блювоту.</VPEH_CorpseExplosion.description>

  <VPEH_WordofOffering.label>word of offering</VPEH_WordofOffering.label>
  <VPEH_WordofOffering.description>Convinces the target to offer their blood to the caster. Can be used on visitors or even during combat.</VPEH_WordofOffering.description>

  <VPEH_SanguineSpear.label>sanguine spear</VPEH_SanguineSpear.label>
  <VPEH_SanguineSpear.description>Launches a pressurized spear of blood over to the target, damaging the target and creating a bloodmist explosion. Damage depends on the caster's hemogen level.</VPEH_SanguineSpear.description>

  <VPEH_BloodRite.label>blood rite</VPEH_BloodRite.label>
  <VPEH_BloodRite.description>Creates a mote of hemogen that follows the caster, acting as an amplifier for psychic sensitivity based on the caster’s current hemogen level.</VPEH_BloodRite.description>

  <VPEH_Bloodstorm.label>bloodstorm</VPEH_Bloodstorm.label>
  <VPEH_Bloodstorm.description>Creates a downpour of blood, inflicting non-hemogenic individuals with bloodmist, causing intense vomiting. Sanguophages instead regenerate hemogen, and don’t gain psychic heat when casting any psycasts under the effects of bloodstorm.</VPEH_Bloodstorm.description>


</LanguageData>